gafesummit.com 2019-05-19

# Privacy Policy - EdTechTeam

At EdTechTeam, we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our customers.

**Information we collect**

We obtain personal information (such as name, contact details, and payment information) when you register on our websites and apps (“site”), place an order, subscribe to emails, attend events, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

In addition, when you visit our websites, use our apps, or interact with our products, we may collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies and web beacons.  A “cookie” is a file that websites send to a visitor’s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A “web beacon”  is a technology that can recognize specific cookies and convey information about that browser. We do not use these technologies to collect PII.

**Use and sharing of information**

Our brands use information collected for a variety of business reasons such as:

  * Personalizing and improving your experience with tailored content, information, advertisements, services, and offers (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * Improving customer service with more effectively responses to service requests and support needs
  * Fulfilling product, event and other transactions and purchases

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**How we protect your information**

We maintain appropriate administrative, technical and physical measures in place to safeguard the security of your personal information. However, when you communicate with customer service via email or chat on our websites, these communications may not be encrypted. For that reason, we ask that you do not share sensitive information via these communication channels.

**Your Choices**

With your PII – like the information you give us to fulfill an event registration – you have the option to change or correct your information and the option of not hearing from us again. There are several ways you can control our use of your PII in connection with marketing and promotions.

_To remove your name from our lists._ You can choose to decline communications from us at the point that we request your PII. After we have collected your PII, you can choose to stop our communications or stop us from sharing your information with other companies for their marketing purposes. To exercise any of these options, please contact us by mail, email, or telephone using the contact information below.

_To stop email communications._ If you receive email communications from us and want to opt out of receiving such communications in the future, you can click the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the promotional email.

_To stop collection of geographic location._ If you do not want us to collect your device’s geographic location, you can disable or opt out of that function when you first use the Site or in your device settings. This will prevent you from using some features of the Site.

_Other choices._ Please see below to learn about your choices with regard to interest-based advertising.

**Interest-based Advertising**

We may work with third-party advertising companies that collect and use information about your online activities across sites over time, in order to deliver more relevant advertising when you are using our services and elsewhere on the Internet. This practice is known as interest-based advertising. You may visit [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) to learn more and to opt out of this type of advertising by companies participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance self-regulatory program. We do not operate or control this site, and are not responsible for the opt-out choices available there. Note that electing to opt out will not stop advertising from appearing in your browser or applications. It may make the ads you see less relevant to your interests. If you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies or use a different computer or Internet browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.

**Third party links**

This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about third party sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). The Sites are not intended for children under 13. We do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.edtechteam.com/terms) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

**Your Consent**

By using our sites, you consent to our online privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**EdTechTeam Products Privacy Policy**

The [Product Privacy Policy](https://docs.google.com/document/d/e/2PACX-1vQSZqkoBw2H60O_EPy-NkKokaPhr1npLL64lCYuSWjEWh_ptQ0KmjxmL2jeNZa62GNGkebkQKNQQgZG/pub) explains what happens to any personal data that you provide to us or that we collect from you while you use our software, including browser extensions and mobile apps.

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can email, write, or call us:

EdTechTeam USA  
5405 Alton Parkway  
Suite 5A-305  
Irvine, CA 92604  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#7d1e080e091210180f0e180f0b141e183d181909181e1509181c10531e1210)  
+1.949.407.9051
